let savollar19 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "bench",
      answer: "C. skameyka",
      options: [
        "A. stul",
        "B. kursi",
        "C. skameyka",
        "D. kreslo"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "to confront",
      answer: "A. yuzlashmoq",
      options: [
        "A. yuzlashmoq",
        "B. uchrashmoq",
        "C. ko'rishmoq",
        "D. duch kelmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "daisy",
      answer: "D. moychechak",
      options: [
        "A. atirgul",
        "B. lola",
        "C. chinnigul",
        "D. moychechak"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "dispute",
      answer: "B. bahs",
      options: [
        "A. omad",
        "B. bahs",
        "C. harakat",
        "D. kelishuv"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "horror",
      answer: "C. qo'rquv",
      options: [
        "A. bahs",
        "B. nizo",
        "C. qo'rquv",
        "D. havf"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "incident",
      answer: "A. hodisa",
      options: [
        "A. hodisa",
        "B. jarayon",
        "C. holat",
        "D. vaziyat"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "mist",
      answer: "D. tuman",
      options: [
        "A. bug'",
        "B. par",
        "C. tutun",
        "D. tuman"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "object",
      answer: "B. narsa",
      options: [
        "A. buyum",
        "B. narsa",
        "C. narsalar",
        "D. ashyo"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "orphan",
      answer: "C. yetim",
      options: [
        "A. bola",
        "B. o'smir",
        "C. yetim",
        "D. go'dak"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "to plot",
      answer: "A. fitna uyushtirmoq",
      options: [
        "A. fitna uyushtirmoq",
        "B. tayyorlamoq",
        "C. jamlamoq",
        "D. tuzmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "pregnant",
      answer: "D. homilador",
      options: [
        "A. bo'g'oz",
        "B. og'ir oyoq",
        "C. yukli",
        "D. homilador"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "rage",
      answer: "B. g'azab",
      options: [
        "A. jahl",
        "B. g'azab",
        "C. achchiq",
        "D. nafrat"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "revenge",
      answer: "C. qasos",
      options: [
        "A. o'ch",
        "B. jazo",
        "C. qasos",
        "D. intiqom"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "shame",
      answer: "A. uyat",
      options: [
        "A. uyat",
        "B. gunoh",
        "C. pushaymon",
        "D. afsus"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "to sigh",
      answer: "D. xo'rsinmoq",
      options: [
        "A. nafas olmoq",
        "B. ingramoq",
        "C. pishillamoq",
        "D. xo'rsinmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "to sneak",
      answer: "B. pisib yurmoq",
      options: [
        "A. emaklamoq",
        "B. pisib yurmoq",
        "C. sirg'anmoq",
        "D. yashirinmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "to spare",
      answer: "C. berib yubormoq",
      options: [
        "A. olmoq",
        "B. bo'lishmoq",
        "C. berib yubormoq",
        "D. tejamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "stem",
      answer: "A. poya",
      options: [
        "A. poya",
        "B. novda",
        "C. shox",
        "D. tana"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "supper",
      answer: "D. kechki ovqat",
      options: [
        "A. ovqat",
        "B. taom",
        "C. yemak",
        "D. kechki ovqat"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "tender",
      answer: "B. yumshoq",
      options: [
        "A. yopishqoq",
        "B. yumshoq",
        "C. mayin",
        "D. qattiq"
      ]
    }
];

export default savollar19;